<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Cesario Silva</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Cesario Silva</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 20:41:30 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why I Think Ruby on Rails Is Better Than Next.js</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-i-think-ruby-y-on-rails-is-better-than-nextjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 20:41:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-i-think-ruby-y-on-rails-is-better-than-nextjs/</guid>
      <description>Over the past few days, I’ve been working with Next.js on a project at my company. It’s one of my first serious experiences with the framework. I had briefly tried it before, but chose Svelte instead when working with TypeScript. These days, I prefer Ruby on Rails 8.&#xA;Now that I’ve spent some time building real features with what many call the most popular framework in the world, I honestly can’t understand why it’s so mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Rising</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/books/red-rising/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:31:53 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/books/red-rising/</guid>
      <description>My Thoughts The first Red Rising book was absolutely amazing. I loved all the characters, especially Darrow.&#xA;The story was captivating and intriguing, the world building was spot on and it left me waiting more. The plot twists were on point and caught me off guard. There were countless moments that I spent laughing and waiting to find out more about the story.&#xA;I already started reading the second book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rework</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/books/rework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 21:47:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/books/rework/</guid>
      <description>My Thoughts I loved this book and it totally fits into my view on productivity. When you work, work hard, but when you rest, rest without excuse. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a fan of Deep Work for a long time and this book talks about it as well.&#xA;It also speaks on issues like chaos at work, unorganized jobs, pointless meetings, which I agree with as well.&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to redefine what productivity is and give up those thoughts of working 75 hours a week, this is the book for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 Angry Men</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/movies/12-angry-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 21:39:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/movies/12-angry-men/</guid>
      <description>My Review This film centers on a jury of 12 men who must decide the verdict in the case of an 18-year-old defendant. After the evidence is presented, the jurors are sequestered in a room to deliberate the young man&amp;rsquo;s fate. If found guilty, he will be sentenced to death by the electric chair.&#xA;When the initial vote is taken, eleven jurors vote guilty. Only one, Juror #8, who we later learn is named Mr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How My Love for Tech Pushed Me to Digital Minimalism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-my-love-for-tech-pushed-me-to-digital-minimalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 13:05:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-my-love-for-tech-pushed-me-to-digital-minimalism/</guid>
      <description>My Love for Technology From the earliest days I can remember, my passion for technology, electronics, and engineering was ever-present. I recall sitting at my father’s old ASUS laptop before I even knew how to write, meticulously typing out a short password from memory. It was my gateway to exploration and discovery.&#xA;One of my fondest memories is playing Windows Pinball with my dad for hours. It’s a memory that brings a smile to my face even now.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
